songspksongspk.io 2017-04-24

# Privacy Policy | SongsPk

If you need any more questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by email.  
At http://songspksongspk.io/, the privacy of our visitors is extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the categories of private data is received and picked up by http://songspksongspk.io/ and how it’s used.

 **Log Files**

Like several alternative websites, http://songspksongspk.io/ makes use of log files. the knowledge inside the log files includes internet protocol ( ip ) addresses, style of browser, internet Service provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and variety of clicks to research trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the website, and gather demographic data. ip addresses, and alternative such info aren\’t connected to any info that\’s personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and internet Beacons**

http://songspksongspk.io/ does use cookies to store info about visitors preferences, record user-specific info on which pages the user access or visit, customise web page content supported based on browser kind or other info that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **Double Click DART Cookie**

Google, as a 3rd party seller, uses cookies to serve ads on http://songspksongspk.io/.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie allows it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://songspksongspk.io/ and alternative sites on the net.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our website. Our advertising partners include ….  
Adsterra,  
Infolinks,  
Revenuehits,  
Bidvertiser,  
and others.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that seem on http://songspksongspk.io/ send on to your browsers. They automatically receive your ip address when this happens. alternative technologies ( like cookies, JavaScript, or internet Beacons ) may be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://songspksongspk.io/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of those third-party ad servers for a lot of detailed info on their practices as well as for directions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://songspksongspk.io/’s privacy policy doesn\’t apply to, and that we cannot management the activities of, such alternative advertisers or websites.

If you want to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. more elaborate data about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
